A Guide to the Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) records FA476
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files and Grants, 1
  - Jackson Planning Project, 1985 (Box 90)
  - Info re: reverter clause in Deed 1949 December 16 of GTI land to U.S. (Box 90)
  - Jackson Airport Project (Box 90)
  - Jackson Airport (Box 90)
  - Letters re: contribution of $125,000 by De Witt Wallace Fund #3 to Hudson River Project (Box 90)
  - Project - Victoria International Corporation re. showings of "The Island Web", 1986 (Box 90)
  - A Contribution to the Heritage of Every American (Box 90)
  - MMT Sales Estate of San Souci and Guinea Gut, Virgin Islands (Box 90)
  - St. John's B.V.I - Bermingham, Rydell Estates (Box 90)
  - St. John's B.V.I - Bermingham, Rydell Estates (Box 90)
  - Building Restrictions- St. John- 1996 (Box 91)
  - Parcel #3 Estate - Beverhoutsberg - No. 7 Cruz Bay Quarter, St. John (Box 91)
  - Acid Rain File (Box 91)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation (Box 91)
  - Claims by Guests (Box 91)
  - Conservation Resources Group Project - Develop a plan of protection for certain resources in Jackson Hole (Box 91)
  - U.S. Virgin Islands - Misc. Material re: John D. Rockefeller Jr. (Box 91)
  - JDR Jr. Contributions to National Parks (Box 91)
  - LSR Major Park Related Activities (Box 91)
  - Contributions to JHPI including special note re: Grand Tetons (Box 91)
  - Contributions (Box 91)
  - Projects, 1954-1975 (Box 91)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Deed Presentation by LSR to Oscar Chapman (Box 91)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Legislative History (Box 91)
  - Contributions to ACA, 1958-1976 (Box 91)
  - Children's Earth Fund (Box 91)
  - Land Review Project, 1996 (Box 92)
  - Land Use Review Project, 1995 (Box 92)
  - Land Use Review Project, 1992-1993 (Box 92)
  - Land & Water/Fund Project, 1995 (Box 92)
  - Hudson River Association - Friends of the Hudson Valley (Box 92)
  - Follow up on NYS Park Study, 1994 (Box 92)
  - F.U. Parks, 1996 (Box 92)
  - National Park Foundation - 75th Anniversary - National Park Service - Project Expenses (Box 92)
  - Project (Bond Issue), 1996 (Box 92)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley, 1996 (Box 92)
  - New York State Parks Project (The Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute), 1992 (Box 92)
  - American Rivers, 1996 (Box 93)
  - American Wildlands (Box 93)
  - American Wildlands, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Conservation Fund grt, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Boone and Crockett Foundation (Box 93)
  - 40th Anniversary Virgin Islands National Park, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Land and Water Conservation Fund, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning, 1996 (Box 93)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Fund, 1996 (Box 93)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Scenic Hudson, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Oral History, 3 binders. (Box 94)
  - Report - "Why the Jackson Hole Airport Needs to be Replaced" (Box 94)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Conservation Check List (Box 95)
  - Hudson Valley Study Project - Montgomery Place (Box 95)
  - Rockwood Hall: The Country Estate of the late William Rockefeller (Box 95)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book, 1940-1990 (Box 95)
  - Parks, Politics, and the People (Box 95)
  - Hudson River Project - Save Montgomery Place, 1985 (Box 95)
  - Sale of Shares of Stock Volumes I and II (Box 95)
  - Cabin Furnishing Plan (Box 95)
  - News from the Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government (Box 95)
  - Estimated Excise Tax, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Credit Memos, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Journal Entries, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Payroll Reimbursement, 1997 (Box 96)
  - American Express, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Beveridge & Diamond HLD, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Vouchers A-D, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Vouchers E-H, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Vouchers I-L, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Vouchers M-P, 1997 (Box 96)
  - B.E. Rock, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund re. Medical Reimbursement, 1997 (Box 96)
    Restricted from scholarly access
  - Vouchers O-S, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Vouchers T-Z, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Grants Paid, 1997 (Box 96)
  - William H. Whyte - per GRL same Consultant Fee, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1997 (Box 96)
  - American Conservation Association, 1997 (Box 96)
  - American Rivers, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Friends of the V.I. National Park, 1997 (Box 96)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Conservation Fund, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Glynwood Center, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Historic River Towns of Westchester, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 1997 (Box 96)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 1997 (Box 96)
  - National Museum of Wildlife Art, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Scenic Hudson, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Teton Science School, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Wyoming Wildlife Federation (Box 96)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley Project, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Hudson River Valley - Greenway Community Council Project, 1997 (Box 96)
  - A-F (Box 97)
  - G-H (Box 97)
  - I-R (Box 97)
  - S-Z (Box 97)
  - The Adirondack Council (Box 97)
  - American Conservation Association Inc. (Box 97)
  - American Rivers (Box 97)
  - American Wildlands (Box 97)
  - American Wildlands (Box 97)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 97)
  - British Virgin Islands National Parks Trust (Box 97)
  - The Conservation Fund (Box 97)
  - Defenders of Wildlife (Box 97)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Finances (Box 97)
  - Friends ofHudson Valley (Box 98)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley, 1990-1991 (Box 98)
    Filed as received from Ellen Pomeroy.
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport (Box 98)
  - Grand Teton National Park (Box 98)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 98)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 98)
  - Historic Hudson Valley (Box 98)
  - Hudson River Film and Video, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. (Box 98)
  - Hudson River Valley Greenway (Community Council) (Box 98)
  - Island Resources Foundation (Box 98)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning (Box 98)
  - Chronology oftbe Hansen Saga (Box 98)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust (Box 98)
  - Marist College - Poughkeepsie, NY (Box 98)
  - LSR Fund (Box 98)
  - Meetings, 1996 (Box 98)
  - Agenda - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1995 November 1 (Box 98)
  - Agenda - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1994 November 4 (Box 98)
  - Meetings, 1995 (Box 99)
  - Meetings, 1994 (Box 99)
  - Agenda - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1993 October 22; 5 copies. (Box 99)
  - Meetings, 1993 (Box 99)
  - Meetings, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Montana Land Reliance (Box 99)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Federation (Box 99)
  - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 99)
  - National Wildlife Federation GRL, 1994 March 2 (Box 99)
  - Nature Conservancy (Box 99)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 99)
  - River Watch Network (Box 99)
  - Rungius Paintings (Carl) (Box 99)
  - Save tbe Redwoods League (Box 99)
  - Scenic Hudson (Box 99)
  - Stanford University - Institute for International Studies (Box 99)
  - Woodstock Foundation (Box 100)
  - Sustainable Use of Land Project (Box 100)
  - Teton Science School (Box 100)
  - United States Government - Dept.of the Interior - National Park Service (Box 100)
  - United States Government - Dept of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation (Box 100)
  - Virgin Islands National Park (Box 100)
  - Wildlife Habitat Enhancement Council (Box 100)
  - South Street Seaport Museum Files (Box 101)
  - "A-B" (Box 101)
  - "C" (Box 101)
  - "D-G" (Box 101)
  - Agenda for Annual Board Meeting, 1998-2000 (Box 101)
  - "H-L" (Box 101)
  - "M-P" (Box 101)
  - "R" (Box 101)
  - "S" (Box 101)
  - "T-Z" (Box 101)
  - American Rivers (Box 101)
  - Financial Statements and Other Info for 1999/2000, 2 folders. (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting (Box 101)
  - Finances (Box 101)
  - The Long Island Sound Conservation Blueprint (Box 101)
  - Conservation Fund (Box 101)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 101)
  - Applicants - "A-Z" (Box 101)
  - Requests - "A-Z" (Box 101)
  - Grants Correspondence, 1999 (Box 102)
  - American Rivers, 1999 (Box 102)
  - American Wildlands, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Conservation Fund, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Conservation Fund Book Grant, 1999 (Box 102)
  - The Environmentors Project, 1999 (Box 102)
  - NY Conservation Education Fund, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Jackson Hole Conservation Alliance, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 1999 (Box 102)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Fund, 1999 (Box 102)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Save the Sound, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Scenic America, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Scenic Hudson, 1999 (Box 102)
  - South Street Seaport Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 102)
  - Wyoming Wildlife Federation, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Bond Act Project, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Hudson River Valley Project, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Grand Teton National Park Fund, 1999 (Box 102)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valleyre. Book, 1999 (Box 102)
  - American Rivers, 1998 (Box 102)
  - American Wildlands, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Conservancy Historic Battery Park, 1998 (Box 102)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Historic Hudson Grant, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Natural Heritage Trust re. Rockefeller State Park Preserve, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Save the Sound Inc., 1998 (Box 102)
  - Scenic America, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Scenic Hudson, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley, 1998 (Box 102)
  - Minutes - Volumes 4-6, 8,9, 1972-1994; 5 bound volumes. (Box 106)
  - Gene W. Setzer (Box 109)
  - Fred Smith (Box 109)
  - Cathleen D. Stone (Box 109)
  - Russel E. Train (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 109)
  - Papers of: William H. Whyte, Lady Bird Johnson, David S. Sampson, Henry L. Diamond, Laurance S. Rockefeller Biography, Materials are loose and not in a folder. (Box 109)
  - William H. Whyte, 2 folders. (Box 109)
  - Dana S. Creel (Box 109)
  - Mrs. LSR died Thurs. April 17, 1997 (Box 109)
  - Trustees Bios/List: (Box 109)
    Includes: John H. Adams, Frances G. Beinecke, Nash Castro, Charles M. Clusen, William G. Conway, Henry L. Diamond, Dana S. Creel, William Moore Dietel, Clayton W. Frye Jr., Carlisle Humelsine (deceased), Lady Bird Johnson, Fred I. Kent III, George R. Lamb, Wm. B. McHenry, Howard Phipps, Story Clark Resor, Laurance Rockefeller
  - ACA/JHPI- Trustees Bios (Box 109)
    Includes: LSR, David S. Sampson, Horace Albright (deceased), John D. Green (deceased), William H. Whyte, Owen & Davis R Scott Greathead, Attorney, Antonia Grumbach - Resume, Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Funeral Info. 12/1/92, Rockefeller History, Misc.
  - Scenic Hudson, 2000 (Box 113)
    Records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly access, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Entire file open in 2016. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted.
  - Urban Land Institute, 2000 (Box 113)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society, 2000 (Box 113)
  - American Conservation Association Inc., 2001 (Box 113)
    Records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly access, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Entire file open in 2017. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted.
  - Williamsburg Land Conservancy, 2001 (Box 113)
  - The Conservancy Historic Battery Park, 2001 (Box 113)
  - The Environmentors Project, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Land Trust Alliance, 2001 (Box 113)
  - National Environmental Education and Training Foundation, 2001 (Box 113)
  - National Museum of Wildlife Art, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Natural Resources Council of America, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Scenic America, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Scenic America (Exec. Memo), 2001 (Box 113)
  - South Street Seaport Museum, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Teton Science School, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Friends of the Hudson Valley Project, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Hudson River Valley Communities Council Project, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Williamsburg Land Conservancy, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Final Agenda, 2001 November 15 (Box 116)
  - Carmen Reyes (Box 116)
  - Board Meeting, 1999 November 18 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1999 November 15 (Box 116)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 November 18 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting, 1996 October 31 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting, 1995 November 1 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting, 1994 November 4 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting - Sterling Forest Folder, 1992 September 11 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting, 1991 October 11 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting - Jackson, Wyoming, 1990 September 7 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting - Saranac Lake, 1989 September 27 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Annual Board Meeting - SS Imperator, 1988 October 14 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board of Trustees Meeting - Wyoming, 1987 September 3 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board of Trustees Meeting - Westchester, NY, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting - Jackson Wyoming, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting - Williamsburg, 1984 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting, 1983 October 22 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting, 1977 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting, 1976 (Box 116)
  - Agenda - Board Meeting, 1975 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 June 30 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 January 14 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1971 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 (Box 116)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1969 (Box 116)
  - JHPI - Minutes, By-laws and Certificate of Incorporation, 1940-2002 (Box 118)
  - JHPI - Minutes, By-laws and Certificate of Incorporation, 1940-2002 (Box 119)